[Music]
life often brings moments when you need
additional financial support be it your
child's higher education medical
expenses or any other immediate needs
did you know that your ICI credential
traditional policy not only provides
Protection cover and long-term savings
but can also fulfill your short-term
Financial
requirements Avail loans at competitive
interest rates against your IC ICI
credential insurance policy without
compromising on the Financial Security
of your loved ones let's understand the
key features and benefits of loan
against traditional
policy flexible loan amounts to suit
your needs a completely paperless
process for your convenience competitive
interest rates that keep your costs low
get immediate access to funds without
compromising on your future Investments
Quick Loan dispersal within 24 hours and
you can repay
[Music]
online only policies with a surrender
value can be considered for a loan you
can borrow up to 80% of the surrender
value of the policy how to apply for a
loan we have an endtoend digital process
for your
convenience log in to our mobile app or
visit our website
www.life.com to apply apply for loan
enter your login ID and
password click on my policy Tab and
select the policy for the
loan now go to financial transactions
and click apply for
loan use our mobile app for more
convenience and an endtoend loan
process click on the all services
section
select loan against policy and then
apply for
loan or you can visit your nearest ICI
credential
Branch so unlock Financial flexibility
today with ICICI credentials loan
against traditional policy
[Music]